{ "cards":
[
    {
        "front": "Welcome to Kotlincard. The first screen to show on startup is a flash screen followed by a list of any sets if they exist. Tap to see the back of this card.Swipe left to to go forward or go to the next card.",
        "back": "If any sets exist their Name, description and count of flashcards that exist in the set will be displayed."
    },
    {
        "front": "A flashcard set is created by pressing the \"+\" in the main screen navigation bar.",
        "back": "Enter a name, description and section for each new set.  None of the fields need to be unique.  The \"Import URL\"defaults to the Android Programming 3rd chapter 7 (Big Nerd Ranch) on GitHub.com. The Randomize checkbox will randomize the flashcards.  The reverse checkbox will reverse the display of the front and back of the cards."
    },
    {
        "front": "In the new flashcard set screen the save button will persist the new set.",
        "back": "Pressing the return button on the top left will not save the new flashcard set."
    },
    {
        "front": "In the new flashcard set screen \"import URL:\" is the location on the internet of the file to be imported.",
        "back": "Currently only \"https\" and file type of \".json\" is supported.  The json file to be imported must be formated correctly. A example json file correctly formatted is \n   { \"cards\": [\n    {\n        \"front\": \"Gives a placeholder name to a type that is used as part of a protocol\",\n        \"back\": \"associatedtype(typealias is sometimes used to declare the concrete type, but Swifts type inference doesn't require it)\"\n    },\n    {\n        \"front\": \"General-purose, flexible construct that becomes the building blocks of a program.\",\n        \"back\": \"Class\"\n    }\n]\n}"
    },
    {
        "front": "A flashcard set can be edited and deleted.",
        "back": "Swipe left on the applicable set to display a red delete button and swipe right to bring up the edit button."
    },
    {
        "front": "Selecting the set record will bring up the card screen.This screen shows all of the flashcards in that set.",
        "back": "The card screen has the functionality to add, edit, and delete flashcards.  The tab menu has 3 buttons.  Start, ReSet and Import"
    },
    {
        "front": "In the card screen select '+' to bring up the card add screen.  Swipe right to bring up the edit button.",
        "back": "Front and back are required text fields and cannot be empty. The show field is defaulted to true and it determines if the card will be shown during a flashcard session."
    },
    {
        "front": "Swiping left on a flashcard record on the right side will bring up the Edit/Delete buttons.",
        "back": "Selecting Edit will bring up the selected card to be edited.  Save must be selected to persist the card edits, selecting the return arrow will not persist the changes made. Selecting Delete will delete the record."
    },
    {
        "front": "There are 3 buttons on the bottom of the tab bar.",
        "back": "Start - starts the flash cards session, ReSet sets the show field back to True, Import - imports cards into the set if the Import field is in the Set."
    },
    {
        "front": "In card screen the right button on the top bar is a download button.",
        "back": "Select the download buttton and a JSON textscreen will be displayed. Touching the screen will copy the JSON to the clipboard. Touching the the top button (3 verticle dots) will bring up a CSV screen.  Touching the screen will copy the CSV to the clipboard."
    },
    {
        "front": "Select \"Start\" to start the flashcard session.  Tap the screen to see the back of the card.  After reviewing the back of the card swipe left to go to the next card.",
        "back": "This is the back of the flash card which is a different color than the front and should be the answer of the front flashcards.  Tap the screen to return to the front card."
    },
    {
        "front": "If the card is know swipe up to mark the card as know.  Text displaying \"Know it!\" will be displayed on the card. Swiping down will remove \"Know it.\".",
        "back": "Cards marked \"Know it.\" will not be displayed the next time Swiftcards is played, but will remain in the current flashcard session."
    }
]
}